Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons; Records apap200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Prisoner Case Files, 1973-1992; Undated; 3; 4.5 cubic ft.
  - Barfield, Margie Velma - Legal Papers & Psychiatric Evaluations, 1983; 1984; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Barfield, Margie Velma - News Clippings, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Bassett, Gus, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Brasfield, Philip, 1980; 1981; 1983; 1988-1989 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Brown, Joseph Green (A.K.A. Shabaka), 1983-1987 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Bryant, Raymond, 1990 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Bullock, Crawford, 1981-1990 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Clark, Raymond, 1981; 1985; 1988-1990 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Clanton, Earl, 1988 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Coker, Rocky, 1984; 1985; 1988-1990 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Coppola, Frank, 1982; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Darden, Willie - Application for Executive Clemency - Sections- Introduction, AA-LL, 1987 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Darden, Willie - Application for Executive Clemency - Section LL continued, 1987 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 24-25)
  - Darden, Willie - Application for Executive Clemency - Sections- LL-MM (End), 1987 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Darden, Willie - Correspondence, 1979-1988 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Darden, Willie - Photos, 1973; Undated (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Darden, Willie - Darden Committee/ Comite, 1987-1990 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Darden, Willie - Direct Mail Correspondence Program, 1988 (Box 4 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Darden, Willie - Information Packet, Partial, Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Darden, Willie - "Injustice: Innocent Man on Death Row", Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Darden, Willie - Letters & Petitions of Support to Southern Coalition, 1983; 1986-1988; Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Darden, Willie - News Clippings [1/2], 1979; 1981; 1985-1988 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Darden, Willie - Newspaper Clippings [2/2], 1979; 1988 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Darden, Willie - Notes/ Files from Southern Coalition Office, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Darden, Willie - Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Darden, Willie - "Willie Darden Information Packet" Part 1/2, Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Darden, Willie - "Willie Darden Information Packet" Part 2/2, Undated (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Dobbs, Wiley, 1977-1985; 1987 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Evans, John, 1979; 1980; 1983 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Fairchild, Barry Lee, 1989 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Fleming, Myron, 1979-1981; 1986-1987; 1989 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Ford, Alvin, 1980-1985 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Affidavits for Giarratano case, 1989 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 15-16)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Case Summary Packet, Intro. - Appendix R, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Case Summary Packet, Appendix S - End, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Certificates of Death, Barbara and Michelle Kline, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Correspondence & Memos, 1981; 1984-1988 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Correspondence & Memos, 1989 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 21-24)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Correspondence & Memos, 1990 (Box 5 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 25-28)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Correspondence & Memos, 1990; 1992 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Giarratano, Joe - "The Extraordinary Case of Joe Giarratano" by M. Bath (No Original Date), Undated (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano vs. Murray, et. al., Civil Action # 85-0655-R, Undated (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano vs. Murray, et. al., Record # 88-411, 1988-1989 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano vs. Murray, et. al., Record #s 87-7518 and 87-7519, 1987-1988 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano v. Murray, Motion to Dismiss, 1987 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarattano v. Procunier, Civil Action # 83-153-N, 1985-1986 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano v. Procunier, Civil Action # 83-185-N, 1987 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano v. Procunier, Civil Action # 83-185-N, 1988-1989 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano v. Procunier, Petition for Writ of Certiorari, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Giarratano v. Procunier, Record # 89-4003, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Motion for Relief from Judgment, 1989 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Giarratano, Joe - News Clippings, 1983; 1989-1990 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Organization of American States, Human Rights Inquiry, 1988 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Giarratano, Joe - "Origins of Violence" by R. Restak, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Preliminary Injunction Packet, 1986 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Press Index, 1988 October 30-1989 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Giarratano, Joe - Psychological Report, 1990 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 18)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted.
  - Giarratano, Joe - Questions and Arguments on Individual Rights, Undated (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Giarratano, Joe - State of Tennessee vs. Byron Lewis Black, 1990 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Gray, Jimmy Lee - Correspondence [1/3], 1977-1983 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Gray, Jimmy Lee - Correspondence [2/3], 1979-1983; Undated (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Gray, Jimmy Lee - Correspondence [3/3], 1983; 1984 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Gray, Jimmy Lee - General, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Gray, Jimmy Lee - Photo Collection & Felt Heart, 1970s (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Groseclose, William - Correspondence, 1979; 1982-1990 (Box 6 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Groseclose, William, Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 1)
    News Clippings, 1981, 1984-1985, and Legal Papers, 1984-1988, undated.
  - Hill, James, 1983-1986 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Hill, James Douglas - Clemency Information Packet, Intro. - Part K [1/2], Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Hill, James Douglas - Clemency Information Packet, Part L - End [2/2], Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Hill, James Douglas - Photographs, 1981; Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Hutchins, James, 1981-1984 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Hutchins, James, 1983; 1984 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Hutchins, James - News clippings, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Jacob, Clinton, Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 9)
  - King, Amos, 1985; 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Machetti, Rebecca Ann, 1979; 1990; Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Mason, Morris O., 1984-1985 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Neeley, Judith A., 1990 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Prejean, Dalton, 1989-1990 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Smith, Jimmy Lee, 1983-1984 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Spenkelink, John - Anti-Death Penalty Booklets, Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Spenkelink, John - Article: "The Last Sixty-Five Hours of John Spenkelink - A Race With Death", Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Spenkelink, John - Correspondence, 1977-1981; 1983; 1984 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Spenkelink, John - Docu-drama Material, Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Spenkelink, John - Execution Guidelines, ca. 1979 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Spenkelink, John - Legal Papers, 1978-1980; Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Spenkelink, John - News Clippings, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 22-26)
  - Spenkelink, John - News Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Spenkelink, John - News Clippings "Master Copies", 1979 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Spenkelink, John - Petitions for Commutation, 1979; Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Spenkelink, John - Photographs, 1979; 1989; Undated (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Spenkelink, John - Prayer Service Programs, 1979; 1980 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Spenkelink, John - Press Release, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Spenkelink, John - "Tallahassee" Script and "Words from an Actor", 1981; 1982 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Sullivan, Robert A. - Correspondence [1/3], 1973; 1979-1982 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Sullivan, Robert A. - Correspondence [2/3], 1983 January-1983 May (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Sullivan, Robert A. - Correspondence, 1983 June-1983 December; 1984 Spring (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Sullivan, Robert A. - General, 1980; 1982-1984 (Box 7 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Sullivan, Robert A. - Legal Papers, 1979; 1983; Undated (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Sullivan, Robert A. - News Clippings, 1983 (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Washington, David, 1980-1982; 1984 (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Watson, Willie, 1985-1988; Undated (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Weaver, Anthony/ Frankie, 1985; 1988 (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Williams, Robert Wayne, 1981; 1983; Undated (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Wright, Charles, 1985; 1986 (Box 8 (3-Prisoner Case Files), Folder 7)
- Subject Files, 1970-1990; Undated; 4; 2.25 cubic ft.
  These documents highlight people and places from the Coalition's history that were not prisoners or sources of funding. Many of the files document abolition involvement from European branches of Amnesty International, especially Scandinavian countries. More photographs can be found in this series, including benefits held with celebrities Mike Farrell and William Styron, plus photos of the Campaign for Compassion. There are also studies and articles written on death penalty-related issues.
  - Alabama Prison Photographs, 1970s (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Advertisement -Last Rights by Joe Ingle, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Alabama Prison Project, 1979 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Alabama Prison Project [1/2], 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Alabama Prison Project [2/2], 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - American Bar Association - Death Penalty Bill, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - American Civil Liberties Union of Tennessee Bill of Rights Report, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - "American Prisons and Jails...Selected Statistics", ca. 1979-1981 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Amnesty International - Carl Von Essen, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Amnesty International - Denmark, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Amnesty International - General Death Penalty Material, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Amnesty International - Monthly Summaries, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Amnesty International - Sweden, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Amnesty International U.S.A. - New York Public Opinion Poll, 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Amsterdam, Tony - N.Y.U Law School, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Atlanta Chaplaincy Training School - Chattanooga, TN, 1990; Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Article, Strategic and Psychological Considerations Applicable to Systematic Constitutional Challenges to Capital Punishment, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Benefit with Mike Farrell - Contact Prints & Negatives from Photos, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Benefit with Mike Farrell - Photographs & Contact Prints, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Benefit with William Styron, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Benefit with William Styron - Photographs, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Biden, Joe - Death Penalty Bill, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Book Proposal Material - General, 1982-1985; Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Boot Camp Drug Rehab, 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Brain - Development, Role in Violence, 1979; 1987 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Brochure: "In Place of Prison" - Incarceration Alternatives, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - California - San Francisco Examiners, "Image", 1989 January (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Campaign for Compassion Photographs, 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Clearinghouse on Georgia Prisons and Jails - By-Laws & Incorporation Information, 1986; 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Commercial Appeal Article, 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Costs of the Death Penalty, 1986; Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - "Death as a Penalty" Booklet by H. Zehr, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Death Penalty Resistance Project of Tennessee, 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - "Doctor Death" Articles, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - "Drugs, Law Enforcement and Foreign Policy" - Report from U.S. Senate, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Early American Execution Cases, 1800s; 1920s-1950s; Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - "Executive Clemency in Capital Cases" by Stuart Lichten, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Florida- Authorizations for Death Row Visits, 1984-1987; 1989-1990 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Florida Clearinghouse on Criminal Justice, Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Florida Death Row- Photograph of Doug McCray, Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Florida- Death Warrants, 1989 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Florida- Execution Guidelines During Active Death Warrant, 1983 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - General Prison Information, 1986; 1989; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Georgia Commission on Juvenile Justice, 1986-1988 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Ingle, Joe- Photographs from Testimony Before Congress, 1988 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Ingle, Joe- Photographs/General, 1989; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Ingle, Joe- Magazine and Newspaper Articles by J. Ingle, 1978; 1982-1989 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Ingle vs. Tennessee, 1975; 1977; 1979 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - It's Enough to Break Your Heart Manuscript Material, 1986-1987 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - John Howard Association, 1980-1981 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Juvenile Corrections- Tennessee, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Last Rights Publicity Material, 1988; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - "Living Conditions of Death Sentence Inmates in the U.S", 1981 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Louisiana- Prison Photos, Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Lyndhurst Sentencing Study [1/2], 1980-1983; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Lyndhurst Sentencing Study [2/2], 1980; 1983 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Mentally Disabled- News Clippings/Ingle Articles, 1976; 1988 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - News Clippings- Articles Depicting Work of Joe Ingle, 1976; 1980; 1984-1988; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - News Clippings- General Death Penalty Issues, 1979; 1983-1989 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - News Clippings- General Death Penalty Issues, 1970; 1976; 1980-1989 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - News Clippings- General Death Penalty Issues, 1990 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - News Clippings- General Death Penalty Issues, Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - News Clippings- Juveniles, Prison, and the Death Penalty, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - News Clippings With Index, 1984; 1987-1988; 1990 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - People to People European Trip, 1986 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Penitentiary Project- 200 Years, 1990 (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Photographs- Arizona Gas Chamber, Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Political Cartoons/Comic Strips, 1981; 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Prison and Jail Project- North Carolina, 1980; 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 9 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Project Proposals, 1980; 1984; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Project Proposals, Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - "Retributivist Article Against Capital Punishment" by R. Pugsley, 1981 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Scandinavian Criminal Policy and Criminology: 1980-1985 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Sermons, 1975; 1982; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Support Activities for Families of the Condemned, 1985; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Sweden- Swedish Correctional Operations, 1982-1986; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Tennessee- Death Row Conditions Suit, 1984-1985; 1988 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Tennessee- Death Penalty Strategy Meetings, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Tennessee- General Prison Information, 1980-1984; 1988; 1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Tennessee- Sentencing Commission [1/2], 1985-1987 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Tennessee- Sentencing Commission [2/2], 1987-1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Tennessee- State Prison News Clippings [1/2], 1988-1989 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Tennessee- State Prison News Clippings [2/2], 1989-1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Tennessee State Prison- Photographs, 1972; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Testimonials- Joe Ingle [1/3], 1978-1980 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Testimonials- Joe Ingle [2/3], 1981; 1985 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Testimonials- Joe Ingle: Statements & Arguments Packet [3/3], Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Texas- General Death Penalty Files, 1989-1990; 1999 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - United Church of Christ- Dr. Avery Post, 1986-1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - United States Supreme Court Decisions, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - U.S. Department of Justice- Bureau of Justice Statistics, 1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - U.S. Senate- Mark Hatfield Defense of Anti-Death Penalty Stance, 1988 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Virginia Coalition/Marie Deans [1/3], 1987-1989 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Virginia Coalition/Marie Deans [2/3], 1989 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Virginia Coalition/Marie Deans [3/3], 1989-1990 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Virginia- Work Group on Response to Victims, with News Clippings, 1989 (Box 10 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - "Waiting to Die in Pretoria" Booklet, 1990 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Women on Death Row- Manuals, Statistics, Programs, 1987-1989 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Wray, Harmon- Project Return, 1984; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Youth Law Center, 1989-1990 (Box 11 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
- Memorabilia, Undated; 5; 1 folder
  This small series comprises about half a dozen buttons with anti-death penalty slogans, several window stickers with the SCJP hummingbird logo, and a pin that says "Author". Joe Ingle wore the author pin during promotional events for his book Last Rights. This series also includes a large banner used in the Campaign for Compassion.
  - Southern Coalition Buttons & Window Stickers and Joe Ingle "Author" Pin, Undated (Box 11 (5-Memorabilia), Folder 5)